Guide to the Abraham Hayward correspondence files: 1063 items, 1790-1889
The New York Public Library. Carl H. Pforzheimer Collection of Shelley and His Circle.
- [G. M. Underdown?], 3 King's Bench Walk, Temple - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 29 August 1868; HWD 02.015; autograph letter signed
- [Geo. M. Butt?], 17 Eaton Sqre - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 30 January 1856; HWD 08.084; autograph letter signed
- [George Russell], 26 Curzon Street - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 09.069; autograph letter signed
  "May Fair".
- [Georgina Decristown?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 04.060; autograph letter signed
- [Grevelgace?], 40 Ennismore Gardens, S. W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 5 October [no year]; HWD 03.026; autograph letter signed
- [H. B. de Grey], 1 Carlton Gardens - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 31 January 1864; HWD 04.061; autograph letter signed
- [H. B.], 76 [Grosvr. P.?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 09.021; autograph letter signed
- [H. Exeter?], 17 Albemarle N - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 6 March 1855; HWD 04.014; autograph letter signed
- [H. G. (initials on wax seal)] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 7 May 1873; HWD 05.065; envelope only
  with one penny stamp.
- [H. G. Hayler], "Treasury" - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 30 October [no year]; HWD 03.087; autograph letter signed
- [H. Rich], Connington Castle - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 24 October 1869; HWD 06.075; autograph letter signed
- [H. Seigall?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 7 November 1874; HWD 06.038; autograph letter signed
- [H. W.? Watson] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 15 May 1845; HWD 02.014; autograph letter signed
- [H. Wellesley], Oxford - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 14 March 1861; HWD 09.049; autograph letter signed
- [Hall], Portsmouth - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 18 January 1841; HWD 10.099; autograph letter signed
- [Hannah Gottenbuir?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 1 March 1878; HWD 07.074; autograph letter signed
- [Helen Selina Blackiston], 13 Old Burlington St - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, [w/m = 1834]; HWD 03.009; autograph letter signed
- [Helen T. N. Allnie?], 3 Bennett St. St James' S. W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 7 January [no year]; HWD 05.086; autograph letter signed
- [Helen the Second], 39 Grosvenor Place - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 09.001; autograph letter signed
  "Saturday"; with envelope.
- [Henrietta Hagtu?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 07.060; autograph letter signed
- [Henrietta[?] Miller], 23 Bruton St, Berkeley Square - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 03.046; autograph letter signed
- [Henry FitzRoy] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 14 July 1857; HWD 01.030; autograph letter signed
- [Henry FitzRoy], Richmond - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 19 August 1853; HWD 01.028; autograph letter signed
- [Henry FitzRoy], Home Office - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 5 February 1855; HWD 04.010; autograph letter signed
- [Henry Jones], 22 Albion Street Hyde Park W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 26 November 1879; HWD 03.076; autograph letter signed
- [Henry Lennox] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 18 January 1881; HWD 04.027; autograph letter signed
- [Henry Miloracy?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 04.018; autograph letter signed
- [Henry R. Dumfield?], 33 Eaton Place - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 7 January 1856; HWD 08.012; autograph letter signed
- [Henry Roberts] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 31 May 1854; HWD 02.032; autograph letter signed
- [Heny? M.? Hope], London - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 07.094; autograph letter signed
- [Herbert Fisher] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 08.023; autograph letter signed
  with empty envelope addressed to Fisher.
- [Hilton?], Egerton Lodge - to Winchilsea, George James Finch-Hatton, Earl of, 1815-1887, Thursday; HWD 05.029; autograph letter signed
- [Holford], Westonbirt House - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 23 February 1878; HWD 07.057; autograph letter signed
- [Horatia de Wa - -?], 44 Prince's Gardens S. W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 09.031; autograph letter signed
- [Isabella Collier] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Friday"; HWD 04.076; autograph letter signed
- [Isabella Collier] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 9 December 1874; HWD 03.039; autograph letter signed
- [J. __se?] - to Orford, Earl of, HWD 02.065; autograph letter signed
  to Lord Orford: [NOT to Hayward].
- [J. Burrowes?], 2 Belgrave Street - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 07.093; autograph letter signed
- [J. C. Vivian] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 04.074; autograph letter signed
- [J. C. Vivian] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 04.073; autograph letter signed
- [J. C. Vivian] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 04.072; autograph letter signed
- [J. Clay] - to Perry, Erskine, Sir, 1806-1882, 12 February 1870; HWD 03.062; autograph letter signed
- [J. E.? Maberly], Manchester Sqre - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 6 June 1847; HWD 07.085; autograph letter signed
- [J. G. Miles], 75, Cornwall Gardens, S. W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 07.081; autograph letter signed
- [J. George Jeffreys] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 13 June 1873; HWD 07.035; autograph letter signed
- [J. Greenwood], United Service Club - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 20 August 1841; HWD 06.083; autograph letter signed
- [J. H. Temple], 7 Brook St - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 14 February [no year]; HWD 03.007; autograph letter signed
- [J. H? Aidele?], Paris - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 1 December 1862; HWD 09.072; autograph letter signed
- J. J. [Trelawny?], 3 Rutland Gate S. W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 28 March 1865; HWD 01.104; autograph letter signed
  [not Edward John Trelawny - cf. note by D. H. Reiman].
- [J. Mackhenna?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 19 February 1847; HWD 07.031; autograph letter signed
- [J. Meynell Ingram], Hill Street - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 07.091; autograph letter signed
- [J. Mitford] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 01.066; autograph letter signed
- [J. Parke], Ampthill - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 4 January 1856; HWD 08.011; autograph letter signed
- [J. Stephens] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 11 November 1865; HWD 10.029; autograph letter signed
- [J. W.? S. Paget], 7 Cromwell Gardens - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 8 March [no year]; HWD 07.104; autograph letter signed
- [James?]:, Thomastown Castle, Cashel - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 7 March 1871; HWD 02.057; autograph letter signed
- [Janetta Houghor?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 12 April 1862; HWD 07.027; autograph letter signed
- [Jeanes Ginneyrs?] - to "My dear Louisa[?] ", 9 October 1860; HWD 02.023; autograph letter signed
- [John Darlow?], 23 Henrietta St. Cavendish Sq - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Saturday morn"; HWD 05.059; autograph letter signed
- [John R. Corballis] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 28 July 1845; HWD 02.016; autograph letter signed
- [Josephine Geale] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 28 June 1857; HWD 07.047; autograph letter signed
- [Juan Heamyn?], Lisbon - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 16 September 1865; HWD 09.064; autograph letter signed
- [Jules Deveaux], Cabinet du Roi, Palais du Bruxelles - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 1 December 1874; HWD 03.068; autograph letter signed
- [Juliet Carrington?], Royal Court, House of Lords - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Wednesday Evening"; HWD 05.076; autograph letter signed
- [Karolyi], Belgrave Square - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 24 April 1880; HWD 04.009; letter (copy)
  In unknown hand.
- [L. Motley] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 06.035; autograph letter signed
- [L. P.] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 7 June [no year]; HWD 07.008; autograph letter signed
- [Lady Charlotte Guter?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 15 July [no year]; HWD 07.013; autograph letter third person
- [Lady Cranbourne], 1, Mansfield St, Portland Place, W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Thursday"; HWD 07.002; autograph letter signed
- [Lady Erin?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 14 June 1880; HWD 04.071; autograph letter signed
- [Lady St. Germains], Dove St - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 03.034; autograph letter signed
  Probably a daughter of Edward Granville Eliot, Earl of St. Germains.
- [Lady Throckmorton] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 07.003; autograph letter third person
- [Lady William Burney?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 10 June 1874; HWD 03.072; autograph letter signed
- [Lady William Purcell?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 03.075; autograph letter signed
- [Lamartine] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 01.077; envelope only
- [Lord Henry Le - ?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 09.056; autograph letter signed
- [Lord Oxford], Hotel Barbesi, Venesi - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 16 March 1869; HWD 02.075; autograph letter signed
- [Lord West] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 2 July 1834; HWD 04.087; autograph letter signed
- [Lornia? Sidell], Christ Church, Oxford - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 24 March [no year]; HWD 09.086; autograph letter signed
- [Louisa Beauclerk], Chesham Street - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 09.090; autograph letter signed
- [Louise A E. Clullery?], 17, Princes Gardens, S. W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 07.069; autograph letter signed
- [Louise Lowfleer?], Paris - to [?], 17 May [no year]; HWD 09.053; verse letter (copy)
- [Lt. Col. E. Taylor], 16 Carlton House Terrace - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Sunday"; HWD 06.077; autograph letter signed
- [Lt. Col. Edw. Taylor] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 10 April 1858; HWD 06.050; autograph letter signed
  name from labeling on back of letter in another hand.
- [M. A. Marnery?], 23 Percy Street, Bedfore Square - to [?], 13 April [no year]; HWD 08.022; autograph letter signed
- [M. Ashley], Saint James's Palace - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 21 June [no year]; HWD 04.058; autograph letter signed
- [M. Cornelius], 1 Edinburgh Mansions, Victoria Street, S. W - to Winchilsea, Constance Henrietta Paget Finch, Countess of, d. 1878, 25 October [no year]; HWD 05.038; autograph note signed
- [M. E - - ?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 6 January 1856; HWD 09.020; autograph letter signed
- [M. G. Gransbull?], Government House, Madras - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 30 January 1884; HWD 02.059; autograph letter signed
- [M. G. Herbert], 38 Chesham Place S. W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 21 February 1878; HWD 03.040; autograph letter signed
- [M. Lowe?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 4 January 1856; HWD 02.049; autograph letter signed
- [M. Periera] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, May 7 [no year]; HWD 06.085; autograph letter signed
- [M. Periera], 23, Grosvenor Square - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 06.080; autograph letter signed
- [M. Strachey] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Friday"; HWD 04.038; autograph letter signed
- [M. Tereira], 44, Park Street, Grosvenor Square, W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 30 January [no year]; HWD 07.063; autograph letter signed
- [Mae Fleuer], 4, Princes Gate. S. W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 09.080; autograph letter signed
  "Mari" engraved on stationery.
- [Mal. Delipiuy?], [Attent?] Gate House - to [Duc du Malakoff], 12 September 1858; HWD 08.032; autograph letter signed
- [March. de Molières], Madrid - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 4 February 1867; HWD 01.086; autograph letter signed
- [Marie Kelergy?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 07.018; autograph letter signed
- [Marquis du Casa Laigliocci?], 12, Queen's Gate Place - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 29 November 1882; HWD 01.029; autograph letter signed
- [Mary Alderin?], 40 Beaufort Gardens S. W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, Saturday 6 April [no year]; HWD 09.076; autograph letter signed
- [Mary Beatrice Blemmenhapett], 98 Sloane Street - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 31 May 1847; HWD 04.039; autograph letter signed
- [Mary de Bottie?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 19 July [no year]; HWD 07.087; autograph letter signed
- [Mary Petro?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 8 February 1878; HWD 04.077; autograph letter signed
- [Mary S. Hardcastle], 54 Queen's Gate Terrace S. W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 04.028; autograph letter signed
- [Mary Tierney], 20, Chapel Street, Belgrave Square - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Saturday Evg"; HWD 07.001; autograph letter signed
- [Mary Tierney], 20, Chapel Street, Belgrave Square - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, Monday 4th; HWD 07.075; autograph letter signed
- [Matebetre?, Hatchwoods, Winchfield] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 31 March 1878; HWD 07.101; autograph letter signed
- [Matilda J. Grove?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 7 July 1847; HWD 03.037; autograph letter signed
- [Miss C. Kindersley?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 09.095; autograph letter third person
- [Monbeay Morris] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 30 September 1869; HWD 04.063; autograph letter signed
- [Mrs. A. Harvey], 9 Stratford Place W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Friday April 14"; HWD 07.046; autograph letter signed
- [Mrs. Brauel?]:, Speaker's House, Palace of Westminster - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 7 June 1878; HWD 04.056; autograph letter signed
- [Mrs. Harvey] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 17 September 1869; HWD 02.076; autograph letter signed
- [Mrs. Reiduyz?], Funchal - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 19 November 1853; HWD 07.041; autograph letter signed
- [Mrs. Wilson?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 5 September 1859; HWD 06.023; autograph letter signed
- [N. [?] Wieman] - to [Rev. C. Fisher], HWD 06.027; autograph letter signed (fragment)
  top half of letter missing.
- [N. Hildgard], 40 Eaton Place - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 07.103; autograph letter signed
- [N - - ? Baring], 41 Upper Grosvenor Street - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 10.021; autograph letter signed
  a relative of Thomas Baring (1799-1873), banker and politician.
- [Nellie Baldock], 8 Grosvenor Place - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 23 June 1878; HWD 01.088; autograph letter signed
- [Nina Abrennard?], 17 Eaton Place, S. W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Monday"; HWD 07.022; autograph letter signed
- [Oakley?], Rockwood Torquay - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 29 December [no year]; HWD 06.102; autograph letter signed
  with notes.
- [Olive Campbell], Round Oak, Englefield Green, Staines - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 07.023; autograph letter signed
- [Olive Sebright], The Croft, Great Marlow - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, Sunday 17; HWD 07.048; autograph letter signed
- [Owen Howell], Dead Letter Office - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 11 May 1847; HWD 09.043; autograph letter signed
- [P. de Tchikatehef?], Paris - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 2 December 1866; HWD 09.062; autograph letter signed
- [Percival Spencer?], St. James's Place - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 16 October 1869; MISC 3532; autograph letter signed
- [Phillip Francis] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 4 March 1860; HWD 02.052; autograph letter signed
- [R. F. Realetish?], 30 Grosvenor Gardens - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 15 February 1878; HWD 03.045; autograph letter signed
- [R. H? Ripone?], 1, Carlton Gardens, S. W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 1 February 1878; HWD 07.067; autograph letter signed
- [R.? P. Clinton] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 12 January 1855; HWD 06.017; autograph letter signed
- [Rashleigh], 16 Stratford Place - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 07.086; autograph letter signed
- [Richard Bushell?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 04.024; autograph letter signed
- [Richard Bushell?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 10.039; autograph letter signed
- [Robert Talbot], [Pau?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 18 May 1840; HWD 01.010; autograph letter signed
- [Robt. C. LeSenek?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 20 October 1874; HWD 05.058; autograph letter signed
- [Roulouie?], 42 Berkeley Sq. W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 01.072; autograph letter signed
- [Rowland Stanley Errington] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 23 January [no year]; HWD 09.071; autograph letter signed
- [Rt. Honble. M. Srull?], 4 Grosvenor Gate, Park Lane - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 7 January 1868; HWD 04.089; autograph letter signed
- [S. G. Calthrope], Arthingworth, Northampton - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 8 February 1857; HWD 03.070; autograph letter signed
- [Samuel Potter], 36 King Street, Cheapside - to "To the Editor of the Times", 24 December 1874; HWD 04.092; letter (copy?)
  "Indestructibility of Slander"; "Not sent to the Times".
- [Shatford de Redcliffe?], Grosvenor Square - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 15 March 1865; HWD 03.043; autograph letter signed
- [Shepherd] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 12 July 1844; HWD 02.079; autograph letter signed
- [Sir Hudson Lowe, probably the eldest son of the military commander] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 01.063; autograph letter signed
- [Sir Jno. Graham] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 11 January 1857; HWD 02.088; autograph letter signed
- [Sophie Jocelyn?], 30 St. James Place - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 14 January [no year]; HWD 07.068; autograph letter signed
- [Sophie Jocelyn], 30 St. James Place - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Thursday"; HWD 05.082; autograph letter signed
- [Spencer Cowper], 25 FS St. Honore [Paui?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 7 March 1869; HWD 01.011; autograph letter signed
- [Spencer Cowper] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 12 June 1873; HWD 02.012; autograph letter signed
- [Spencer Cowper], Rue du Faubourg Saint-Honoré, Paris - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 2 March 1869; HWD 06.089; autograph letter
- [St.? Christie] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 6 November 1867; HWD 03.063; autograph letter signed
- [Stanley], St. James's Square - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 2 January 1868; HWD 10.057; autograph letter signed
- [Stephen Olclirig?], [Clemment's Lane?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 26 January 1858; HWD 06.074; autograph letter signed
- [Stockes?], House of Commons - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 25 July 1871; HWD 02.061; autograph letter signed
- [Stockes], The Athenaeum - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 17 December 1866; HWD 02.073; autograph letter signed
- [Strde R?], Hastings - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 19 January 1876; HWD 10.027; autograph letter signed
- [Sybella Ashley], 61, Cadogan Place - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 4 March [no year]; HWD 07.071; autograph letter signed
- [T. W. Phillippe]: - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 13 July 1847; HWD 04.067; autograph letter signed
- [Thomas C. Briel?], Cullen - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 03.002; autograph letter signed
- [Thomas Clark] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 19 March 1844; HWD 05.095; autograph letter signed
- [Thomas Hobhouse], Temple - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 2 June 1845; HWD 01.085; autograph letter signed
- [Virginia Goldmayer?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Sunday"; HWD 04.079; autograph letter signed
- [Vivian], War Office - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 22 July [no year]; HWD 02.064; autograph letter signed
  War Office stationery.
- [W. Davies] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 24 December 1854; HWD 01.064; autograph letter signed
- [W. Dawes?], 13 Queen Square - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 9 December 1856; HWD 10.009; autograph letter signed
- [W. Dawes?], 13 [Owen?] Square - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 10 December [year illegible]; HWD 06.044; autograph letter signed
- [W. Dawes?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 7 January 1856; HWD 05.071; autograph letter signed
- [W. Dawes?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 11 December [year illegible]; HWD 06.073; autograph letter signed
- [W. F. Firlason?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 23 January 1868; HWD 09.073; autograph letter signed
- [W. Free Garrow?], London - to Jeffson, William Garrow, 6 November 1806; HWD 04.036; autograph letter signed
  addressed to Jeffson at Pegwell Cottage, Ramsgate; recipient = the grandson of the writer.
- [W. G. Blackie], Edinburgh - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 15 November 1860; HWD 02.082; autograph letter signed
- [W. H G.? Mildmay] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Thursday"; HWD 07.009; autograph letter signed
- [W. H. Thompson], Trinity Lodge, Cambridge - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 7 January 1858; HWD 03.078; autograph letter signed
- [W. P. Ward] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 6 February 1856; HWD 10.105; autograph letter signed
- [W. P. Ward], 31 St. George St - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 3 June 1857; HWD 10.035; autograph letter signed
- [W. Whe - ?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 27 April 1855; HWD 08.034; autograph letter signed
- [Wm. Alex. Smith], New York - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 7 February 1862; HWD 09.070; autograph letter signed
- [Z? C] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 12 January 1858; HWD 08.079; autograph letter signed
- [Zillie Zaugtry?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 29 July 1878; HWD 10.095; autograph letter signed
- [Zillie Zaugtry?], 18 Albert Mansions, Victoria St - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 06.095; autograph letter signed
  with envelope;.
- [Zoe Fleosou?], Bishopthorpe, York - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 11 March [no year]; HWD 03.033; autograph letter signed